sluniverse.com 2008-06-18

# Privacy Policy Statement

The text regarding the use of third party ad servers was changed to reflect that ads provided by the LinkShare Network's service have been added to the site. Their own privacy policy can be viewed at [ www.linkshare.com](http://www.linkshare.com/). Also added text regarding notification of changes to privacy policy.

Snapzilla user registration - registered SLUniverse.com forum users are now able to use their SLU login to sign into the Snapzilla site. To support this feature, it is necessary to associate their avatar name with their SLU account by sending an email postcard to /FONT>

 **4/5/2005 - Update to Privacy Policy** The email addresses  [ private@sluniverse.com](mailto:private@sluniverse.com) and [ private@slpics.com](mailto:private@slpics.com) have been added to provide individual opt out controls on a per snapshot basis of location information being displayed on the Snapzilla site. **

4/2/2005 - Update to Privacy Policy

** To support a change added to the email postcards in version 1.6 of Second Life, the location information (sim name and x/y coordinates) of each snapshot is being saved in addition to the information listed below that is saved as part of processing the email. The display of exact coordinates will be an opt out feature of Snapzilla - pictures will be filterable by sim name.

A new feature has been added to Snapzilla that allows users to email snapshots to a friend. The names and email addresses the snapshots are sent to and from are not tracked or saved. The only tracking being done is a count of how many times each snapshot has been sent. 

Policy Statement

This is the web site of SLUniverse.

We can be reached via e-mail at [ support@sluniverse.com](mailto:support@sluniverse.com)

For each visitor to our Web page, our Web server automatically recognizes only the consumer's domain name, but not the e-mail address (where possible).

We collect only the domain name, but not the e-mail address of visitors to our Web page, aggregate information on what pages consumers access or visit, information volunteered by the consumer, such as survey information and/or site registrations.

The information we collect is not shared with other organizations for any purpose.

With respect to cookies: We use cookies to store visitors preferences, record session information, such as login information.

If you supply us with your postal address on-line, you would only ever be contacted at this address for dispute resolution of financial transactions.

Persons who supply us with their telephone numbers on-line will only receive telephone contact from us after unable to successfully contact you in case of dispute resolution of financial transactions.

With respect to Ad Servers: _We use the services of both our own internal ad server and The LinkShare Network._

Upon request we provide site visitors with a description of information that we maintain about them.

Consumers can access this information by e-mail us at the above address.

Upon request we offer visitors the ability to have inaccuracies corrected in contact information, unique identifiers.

Consumers can have this information corrected by sending us e-mail at the above address.

With respect to security: When we transfer and receive certain types of sensitive information such as financial information, we redirect visitors to a secure server. We have appropriate security measures in place in our physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you at our site.

If you feel that this site is not following its stated information policy, you may contact us at the above email address addresses, the Federal Trade Commission by phone at 202.FTC-HELP (202.382.4357) or electronically at  http://web.archive.org/web/200502250.../complaint.htm.

_To the maximum extent permitted by applicable law, SLUniverse reserves the right to change or replace this Privacy Policy at any time and from time to time without prior notice to or the consent of any person. Any changes or replacement will be posted at this site._
